They also used a picture of you, and you like bad teeth, Mr. Kinch?
Yes.
Is it just the row of teeth? Bad teeth.
Or the eyes? Are your eyes good too?
My eyes are good.
I don't have ear tabs, but I'm surprised.
Thin.
But what did you feel pain in? The ear tabs.
No sensation.
No matter how hard I grabbed.
What? Are you sure?
I'm totally fine.
No, no, no, no, pulling hurts!
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, I'm just fine with the pulling.
That hurts.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, no, no, you said it doesn't hurt.
It hurts when you goof on it. It hurts when you do it like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, my precious girl!
That's a lot of girls!
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
And I want you to take on the world.
Goodbye!
This show is a laugh key, where Ana-chan tries all kinds of things.
This is Ano's third time.
Okay, well, let's say this is the third time.
Yes, yes, well, let's just say it's the third time.
Because if you don't enjoy it, they don't give you points.
Um, I want to die after eating.
That's enough.
Things to do after eating.
It's hard to brush my teeth.
Correct.
Yay.
I don't know what to do with two rows of teeth.
Didn't your dentist teach you how to brush two rows of teeth?
I did. He gave me a toothbrush that I had never seen before.
I can't use that every day.
It's not sticky anymore. That's my biggest problem.
This is it.
I'm trying not to mention No. 1, but I want to say it now.
I want to say that I've already said No. 1 in this series of events up to now.
A lie.
I always want to say that.
Is that so?
How many more times do I have to answer?
I don't care how many times.
I don't care how many times you say it.
I think about it all the time. That's exactly what I think about most at times like this.
Yeah, that's why people envy me. Do they envy me? What I always think. This is exactly what I think most at times like this.
Yeah, that's why they envy me.
Do they envy you?
Well, I don't know, but they like someone like me,
I'm embarrassed.
No, no, no, not at all. Not at all.
I'm scared. Scary.
So, on the other hand, if you had teeth like that,
What would you think if you had teeth like that?
What would you think if you had those teeth?
I would definitely not want them to look at me.
Do you really like them? You have bad teeth.
No, I don't. I'm ashamed of mine, but I like other people's.
Well, let me give you a big hint, for example,
I think about what I think when someone asks me, "Are you not good to eat? That's what I think when people ask me.
I don't have that much trouble with my teeth.
So why do you think it doesn't bother me?
There are more important things than teeth.
It's not that deep.
I'm going to go now.
Yes, this way.
I don't see what the inconvenience is in the first place. Oh, I see.
This is why I get told this so often. Isn't it hard to eat? I say, "Yes, it is,
I've never lived with normal teeth.
I don't even know if it's easy or hard to eat.
Oh, that's funny!
So people often ask me, "Isn't it hard for you to talk? I'm often asked, "Isn't it hard for you to talk?
I don't know if it's easy to talk or not.
That's great!
So, I don't know if that's true or not.So, more to the point, I'm not sure if this is really true anymore.
Hmmm.
I have no idea. It's been this way for a long time.
Wow, that's cool.
No, no, it's not cool.
No, it's cool!
It's like those cartoon characters.
You there? No, I've always been this way.
I don't know, I was born this way.
Ha-ha-ha. Well, no, I've always been like this. I don't know, it's the one I was born with.
Well, no, it's cool.
But I like this No. 1 answer. It was my favorite answer.
Oh, good, good, good. I was already second and third for this one, so it's not too much to say.
So, 2 points.
Yay!
What do you mean I get points?
Well, because it was fun.
Even though it was fun.
Let's see Eguchi-san brush his teeth. Applause.
No, don't look.
I'm going to show you his teeth later.
I'd like you to see me brush my teeth, since I got a lot of bites before that.
So you'll look at the teeth in the end?
Yes, I will.
So, before that, I want to remove something that shouldn't be seen on camera.
I don't think there is such a thing.
Show me how you brush.
What do you want me to do?
Polish as usual.
I don't have this kind of situation.
I'll do it.
Just like usual.
It's better if you open your mouth.
That's enough then. He's been in the back since then, right? She's complaining. Then, you're not a normal person, are you?
That's why you're at the back.
She's complaining.
So, like this...
Like this.
Wow!
You go from the bottom.
I guess so.
And here we go, right?
Right there, right there.
Right here.
Why there?
It's here, so we have to go like this.
We'll do the gap, so we have to go like this.
Do the gap already?
The bottom feather?
Do the gap like this.
If I did it, I'd do it like that.
It's the only way to do it.
I try to do it this way.
The back side?
It's not difficult to do the back side like this.
So I'll do it like this.
And here, like this... wow... What happened to Mayaba's back teeth? There is no Mayaba in the back, originally!
The back mayaba has to go from here, then.
Wow! Wow, wow, wow!
That's so amazing...the security is so strong.
I don't use the mayava much, when I eat.
Oh, really?
I always eat only with my back teeth.
So I don't get anything stuck here.
I don't have a cavity here. I don't think I'll get a cavity here.
There are three cavities on the bottom. What?
I've got three more before I know it. Are you kidding me?
What?
Oh, my God!
That's amazing.
You're already looking at it.
I'm sorry. You're already looking at it.
I'm sorry for sure. It's okay, but I can't tell you how much this makes me feel like, honey...
I have to do more than that. So, I've been given some weird equipment, which I don't use.
I don't use them... but I use them...
It's like a graveyard.
That's a bad analogy.
It's like a tombstone, right? Boseki boseki.
The back front teeth? Yeah.
Cool. It's not cool, no matter what you think.
So often, I'm asked... and this isn't one of them, but I'm asked..,So often, and this is not that one I mentioned earlier, people ask me,
I'm often asked if things don't get stuck in the gaps between these teeth,
Because there is too much space between the teeth, so they don't get stuck.
I can take it out when it's stuck. I could get it out with a thump.
You couldn't even get corn in there, could you? It doesn't go in. It's surprisingly easy to take it out. The corn didn't go in, did it?
It didn't go in. Surprisingly, it didn't go in.
I only got two pieces.
But in the meantime, I did.
You can't put the corn between the corn and the date.
But when I go on a date with you, I want you to put corn on the cob.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's so nice, right?
It's so embarrassing, coming here on a date.
If there's too much corn in here.
I'd think it's really cool.
Oh, no, the whole town will laugh at you.
It's great, isn't it?
People would say, "Why don't you have a sense of humor? It's so big and there's such a big thing in between.
That's what's so good about it, that's what makes it interesting.
The knitting is like this.
Then, what is the point of this game?
This was a game?
Yes, it was.
It's one point!
One point! Wasn't it pretty good?
I mean, there was a lot of, like, wow, but not that much.
I mean, I got to see her brush her teeth, but I didn't get to see her put them down properly.
It's frustrating, so I'll give you 1.
1, that's a total of 4 points.
One more point, and it's five.
I'll get to 5.
I'll do my best, believing that something will happen when I get to 5.
I'll do my best.
Let's see your teeth, child care! Any applause?
Well, what do you mean, "look"?
It's the iPhone, which is all the rage these days.
It's been a fad for quite a while.
I'll zoom in.
What are you going to do with it?
Oh, you're gonna flush it.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
But wouldn't it make a great video?
No, I'm just saying, you know, I've already said I'd like to see your teeth.
This is about as close as I'm going to get.
Oh...
I mean, you're getting all the way in there.
Oh, man.
Oh my God, I'm scared.
I really hope you guys don't have a problem with this.
Caution.
It has to be a "viewer warning".
It's a warning, really.
It's on YouTube, isn't it?
Are you okay? Like a van.
I have to be careful.
Are you okay?
Okay, I'll take a look.
Do you want me to open it? Open your mouth.
Open your big mouth.
Wow! Look at this! It's like a jewelry box!
No, it doesn't.
But it does look like jewelry.
It's kind of...
Wait a minute!
Because Aymon is getting in my mouth!
Wow! If it was pretty clean...
And in the back... wow! Wow!
Wow, look at this.
Here's a cemetery.
Here comes the cemetery zone.
Wow.
I'd like to see the side view.
Look at this.
Oh, my God, look at this angle from the teeth.
You don't get to see this angle from my teeth.
Which is more embarrassing, being naked or not?
But you're okay with nudity.
I mean...
Nudity is OK with you?
Shut up!Shut up!
Don't talk to me like that!
Open your mouth.
Oh, wow!
That's amazing! Look at this!
It's like a cave!
Oh, my gosh! Jewelry, please! It's like a cave! Oh, my God!
There's a gem stuck in it. It's common in caves, right?
You know, blue, with gems and stuff hanging from them.
Wow!
Look, guys! Here, from the side.
Look!
Right here, right here.
Here's a great shot. And from the mouth.
Wow, I can't believe this is human. It's beautiful.
But, I think this side here is a little bit dirty.
May I have a word? I really don't like it.
Why? Why?
You're looking at something amazing.
Oh, no, not yet.
I'm looking at something amazing right now, guys.
You're looking at something amazing right now, guys.
It's so valuable, I think every dentist in the country is looking at it right now.
I think every dentist in the country is looking at it right now.
There's so many silver plates. They're dirty. It's been theatrical a lot.
It's no good, maybe. It's the way he brushes his teeth.
Look at the back here.
May I have your attention, please? Can I ask you to focus on the nose line?
The mess.
No, it's fine.
I don't like it.
This is a little bit more human than the other people who have a well-groomed nose,
But it doesn't have a human touch.
What do you mean? You don't have a human touch? After all.
A humanistic dirtiness, and yet an arrangement with no human touch?
That's the worst, isn't it?
That's why it's so great.
It's not human, it's dirty, dirty, dirty. What's the point!
Maybe it's art. And this graveyard.
Who is it? Someone must be dead.
Oh, shit! I'm talking so much! I'm so happy!
If this gets on YouTube, I'll watch it back. Thank you. Yay! This will be seen by jankog people.
Please don't do that, really.
Thank you very much.
Can you please stop posting it?
I'll put it up.
I'm so moved, I'm on my way, it's amazing.
I was in a cave in a strange world, and wow, it was like I was stuck in a jewel I'd never seen before.
And I was drooling and sparkling.
Is there anyone else in the world who likes it?
Yes!
Is it okay?
I'm sure there is.
Yes, the point of this game is..,
100,000 points!
What was that? That was early in the game!
That's why I was so happy.
Oh, thank goodness. 100,000 points?
There's a prize.
Yes! Is it really there?
Is it really there?
What do you think?
What's this?
It's a tooth I made.
This is the model.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is a graveyard.
Yes, it is!
And what's with the realistic blackening of that unpolished area?
What's this? Why did I make it like this?
Why are they like this? My teeth.
Yes, they are. Lesson learned, don't forget.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What did you think of them?
Well, they were dirtier than I expected.
No, it's not good. It's dirty.
It was like a black hole, far beyond what I had imagined, and I loved it.
So it was good, then.
Yes, I loved it.Yes, I love it.
Let's say it's good.
If anything happens with the leafy child, it's for wild tea.
Yeah.
No, no, no, I'm not the one to discuss it with the leaf girl.
I'll go to Aisa-san. I'll get all your teeth sent to me too, lots of them.
Hey, stop those guys already, seriously! What the hell are they doing!
I like it. Send them to me.
Don't send them! Don't do it.
Let's recreate Mr. Iguchi's teeth in Metaverse space so that you can see them there.
Oh, that's good! It's really good!
What do you mean? You want to build a cave of my teeth in the Metaverse?
Oh, no! You want to build a cave of my school in the Who Wants to Go There?
Who wants to go there?
I want to go there! It's fun!
And there's a cover.
Thanks!
Amachannel, subscribe to our channel!